

PERSONAL DETAILS

Surname Roberts
First Names Jihaad

ID Number 000111 5227 082

Gender Male

Nationality South African

Address 21 Portland Road, Salt River 7925

Contact Number 064 503 0924

Email Address jihaadroberts@gmail.com
Social Media jihaadroberts@gmail.com
Instagram.com/mr_roberts22

Driver's License No

Languages English, Afrikaans, Arabic(Basic)

PROFILE

Game Developer/Photo editor/video editor/web developer/software developer(basic and still learning) with 2+ years experience of coding in C#/HTML/CSS/Javascript and basic python. I am able to use the Unity game engine for game development. I Also contain 2+ years experience using Visual Studio and Visual Studio Code and is also able to do basic 3D modelling using the Blender software and advanced photo editing and video editing using Adobe Photoshop and Filmora9 software respectively.

EDUCATION

 Al Azhar High School, Cape Town (Jan 2016 – Nov 2019)

Matriculated Subjects:

- English
- Afrikaans
- Mathematics
- Physical Science
- Biology
- Arabic
- Life Orientation
- Madina Institute, Cape Town (Jan 2020 – May 2020)

OTHER

- Learn C#, Code Academy (Nov 2019 – Jan 2020)
- Learn HTML, Code Academy (Jan 2020 – Mar 2020)
- Learn CSS, Code Academy (Mar 2020 – Jun 2020)
- Learn JavaScript, Code Academy (Jun 2020 – Sep 2020)
- Learn Python, Solo Learn (Sep 2020 – Sep 2020, didnt finish)
- Learn ASP.NET, Razor Pages (Jun 2021 – Aug 2021)

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Mechanic Assistant at Jumbo Parts, Cape Town (Jan 2018 – Mar 2018)
 - Job mostly included the stripping of car parts, carrying of tools and the occasional stock take.
- Installer's Assistant at Revelation Audio, Cape Town (Jan 2019 – June 2019)
 - Job included the carrying of heavy tools, drilling, grinding, gluing and stock take.
- Waiter at Classique Cafe (weekends only), Cape Town (Jan 2021 – April 2021)
 - Job included the carrying of heavy tools, drilling, grinding, gluing and stock take.
- Programmer and Photo Editor at Kaotec, Cape Town (July 2020 – March 2021)
 - Job included debugging of pre existing code, improving existing programs and Retouching using Adobe Photoshop.

TECHNICAL/SPECIAL SKILLS

- Able to code in C#,HTML,CSS,Javascript and basic Python.
- Basic 3D modelling using Blender software
- Can solve a Rubiks Cube in under 30 seconds
- Sketching
- Wordpress web development
- Adobe PhotoShop
- Unity

OTHER SKILLS

- Active listening
- Hardworking with unyielding tenacity to succeed at anything I put my mind to.
- Presentation and public speaking.
- · Creativity and problem solving
- Teamwork

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Developed an android game called "Sky High" currently available on Playstore.

HOBBIES / INTERESTS

Chess, soccer, coding/computer programming, solving puzzles, reading and artificial intelligence.

PERSONAL GOAL AND OBJECTIVES

My personal goal is to start multiple companies/streams of income in order to achieve financial freedom and support my family and those in need by utilizing my full potential and skills. My personal objectives are to deliver the best performance, regardless of the challenge given to me, to always maintain good working skills and relationships with colleagues and clients/customers, to never give up and always create room for self-development.

I, Jihaad, declare that the particulars furnished above are true and correct. I enclose my CV for your consideration. I would like to tell you more about my suitability for the role at interview and would be pleased to meet with you. Thank you for your time assessing through my curriculum vitae.

0645030924, jihaadroberts@gmail.com